<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Data Wrangling and Data Exploration  Lily Tapia (lmt2622) Instructions A knitted R Markdown document (ideally HTML) and the raw R Markdown file (as .Rmd) should both be submitted to Canvas by 11:59pm on the due date. These two documents will be graded jointly, so they must be consistent (i.e., don’t change the R Markdown file without also updating the knitted document).
The text of the document should provide a narrative structure around your code/output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Modeling  Lily Tapia (lmt2622) Guidelines and Rubric  0. (5 pts) Introduce your dataset and each of your variables (or just your main variables if you have lots) in a paragraph. What are they measuring? How many observations?  My dataset, ‘CollegeDistance’, involves data from a survey conducted by the Department of Education in 1980. There is a total of 14 variables of this dataset and 4739 observations. There are 8 categorical variables which include ‘gender’, ‘ethnicity’, ‘fcollege’ (if the student’s father was a college grad), ‘mcollege’ (if student’s mom was a college grad), ‘home’ (whether or not the family owns a home), ‘urban’ (if the school is in an urban area),‘income’ (if family income is above $25,000/year) and ‘region’ (West region or other).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>R and Python</title>
      <link>/post/2021/05/08/blog-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2021/05/08/blog-post/</guid>
      <description>Coding with R and Python One thing that is cool about R is that you can easily transfer codes/objects from R to Python and vice versa. Below is an example of how you can do this.
First, load the reticulate package in R and define your object (which could be anything really). In this case, I will be defining “This is my” as the object “dog”.
#R code chunk library(reticulate) dog&amp;lt;-&amp;quot;This is my&amp;quot; Now, define “dog” (or the assigned name you used above) as an object in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>    </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
